http://www.bradleycollection.com/privacy-notice/

Visitors to our websites
When someone visits www.bradleycollection.com we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. If we do want to collect personally identifiable information through our website, we will be up front about this. We will make it clear when we collect personal information and will explain what we intend to do with it.
Analytics cookies – We use web analytics services to help us understand how people use our site. For example, we can see which parts of the site are most popular and identify if errors occur.
Cookies allow web analytics services to recognise your browser or device and, for example, identify whether you have visited our site before, what you have previously viewed or clicked on, and how you found us. The information is anonymous and only used for statistical purposes. It allows us to track information, such as how many individual users we have and how often they visit our websites. They are anonymous and do not contain or collect any information that identifies you.
When you are viewing a website, a cookie is transferred to your browser by the web server and is stored on your computer. It can only be read by the server that gave it to you.
These web analytics services are designed and operated by other companies on our behalf.
Managing analytics cookies – It is possible to opt out of having your anonymous browsing activity within websites recorded by analytics cookies. The Bradley Collection uses Google Analytics, you can opt out of their cookies by clicking on the following link. Please note that this will take you to the relevant third party’s website and generate a ‘no thanks’ cookie, which will stop any further cookies being set by those third parties.
Don’t forget that by not allowing analytics cookies, this stops us from being able to learn what people like or don’t like about our site so that we can make them better.
Subscribers to our website – individuals registering to use the extra functionality are required to provide e-mail address and create a password. They may also include business, personal, delivery address and other contact details. Data is protected online by the security provided by the WordPress software employed to create the site. Any personal data provide will not be shared with any other organisation and will only be used by us for marketing purposes provided express permission to do so has been granted. Individuals will have the right to view data held and to request deletion by contactingthedataprotectionofficer@bradleycollection.com
Online surveys
We collect information volunteered by individuals using an online survey tool provided by Survey Monkey. Any personal data provided may be stored indefinitely, will not be shared with any other organisation and will only be used by us for marketing purposes provided express permission to do so has been granted. Individuals will have the right to view data held and to request deletion by contacting thedataprotectionofficer@bradleycollection.com
People who contact us via social media
We use a third party provider, Clear & Creative Ltd to manage our social media interactions. Personal data may be volunteered by individuals using DM and PM functionality within social media platforms. Any personal data provided may be stored indefinitely, will not be shared with any other organisation and will only be used by us for marketing purposes provided express permission to do so has been granted. Individuals will have the right to view data held and to request deletion by contacting thedataprotectionofficer@bradleycollection.com
People who call us
We do not record telephone calls and any personal data volunteered to us during a telephone conversation may be stored indefinitely, will not be shared with any other organisation and will only be used by us for marketing purposes provided express permission to do so has been granted. Individuals will have the right to view data held and to request deletion by contacting thedataprotectionofficer@bradleycollection.com
Credit card details provided to us by telephone are never recorded, written down or otherwise stored other than via the contemporaneous entry of the data into our credit card payment processing system. We also employ protocols to minimise the risk that your details may be overheard.
People who email us
Any personal data volunteered to us by e-mail will be secured via our general security software and protocols. Data (including the e-mail address used for contact) may be stored indefinitely, will not be shared with any other organisation and will only be used by us for marketing purposes provided express permission to do so has been granted. Individuals will have the right to view data held and to request deletion by contactingthedataprotectionofficer@bradleycollection.com
We will monitor any emails sent to us, including file attachments, for viruses or malicious software. Please be aware that you have a responsibility to ensure that any email you send is within the bounds of the law.
We never request credit card details by e-mail and request that these never be sent by this method as it is not secure.
Job applicants
The Data Protection Officer of The Bradley Collection Ltd is the data controller for the information you provide during the application process unless otherwise stated
All of the information you provide during the process will only be used for the purpose of progressing your application, or to fulfil legal or regulatory requirements if necessary.
We will not share any of the information you provide during the recruitment process with any third parties for marketing purposes or store any of your information outside of the European Economic Area. The information you provide will be held securely by us whether the information is in electronic or physical format.
We will use the contact details you provide to us to contact you to progress your application. We will use the other information you provide to assess your suitability for the role you have applied for.
What information do we ask for, and why?
We do not collect more information than we need to fulfil our stated purposes and will not retain it for longer than is necessary.
The information we ask for is used to assess your suitability for employment. You don’t have to provide what we ask for but it might affect your application if you don’t.
Offer of employment
If we make a conditional offer of employment we will ask you for information so that we can carry out pre-employment checks. You must successfully complete pre-employment checks to progress to a final offer. We are required to confirm the identity of our staff, their right to work in the United Kingdom and seek assurance as to their trustworthiness, integrity and reliability.
You will therefore be required to provide:
Proof of your identity – you will be asked to attend our office with original documents, we will take copies.
Proof of your qualifications – you will be asked to attend our office with original documents, we will take copies.
We will contact your referees, using the details you provide in your application, directly to obtain references
If we make a final offer, we will also ask you for the following:
Bank details – to process salary payments
Emergency contact details – so we know who to contact in case you have an emergency at work
How long is the information retained for?
If you are successful, the information you provide during the application process will be retained by us as part of your employee file for the duration of your employment plus 6 years following the end of your employment. This includes your criminal records declaration, fitness to work, records of any security checks and references.
Individuals will have the right to view data held by contacting thedataprotectionofficer@bradleycollection.com
Current or former employees
The list below details some of the data that we may hold on employees:
Name, residential address, telephone and e-mail address.
Date and place of birth.
Nationality.
Proof of identity – copies of original documents.
Proof of qualifications – copies of original documents.
Bank details
Emergency contact details
Employment history
Medical history
Absence and sickness history
Disciplinary history
This is all held securely in locked physical files, accessible by directors of the company only and/or in a secure segment of the company’s network, accessible to directors only.
How long is the information retained for?
Data will be retained by us as part of your employee file for the duration of your employment plus 6 years following the end of your employment.
Individuals will have the right to view data held by contacting thedataprotectionofficer@bradleycollection.com
Lawful basis for processing personal data
We use ‘consent’ and ‘fulfilment of contract’ as the lawful bases for processing personal data.
Complaints or queries
The Bradley Collection Ltd tries to meet the highest standards when collecting and using personal information. For this reason, we take any complaints we receive about this very seriously. We encourage people to bring it to our attention if they think that our collection or use of information is unfair, misleading or inappropriate. If you want to make a complaint about the way we have processed your personal information, you can contact us using the contact details below:
Changes to this privacy notice
We keep our privacy notice under regular review. This privacy notice was last updated on 13 April 2018.
How to contact us
If you want to request information about our privacy policy you can email us on thedataprotectionofficer@bradleycollection.com or write to:
The Data Protection Officer
The Bradley Collection Ltd.
Lion Barn • Maitland Road • Needham Market • Suffolk • IP6 8NS • UK
T +44 (0)1449 722724 • F +44 (0)1449 722728
www.bradleycollection.com
Registered Office as above • Registered Number: 2681557 • Vat No: 524571060
call
world +44 (0)1449 722724
US & Canada +1 (310) 815 8255
email
info@bradleycollection.com
info.us@bradleycollection.com
follow
Instagram
feed
RT @CDWfestival: Rootwork & Conjure are new additions to the Change Agent collection from #CDW2021 exhibitors @MillikenEurope. Rootwork is…10 days ago
home
search
philosophy
terms of use
email disclaimer
privacy notice
collections
gliderpole
